- 菲比   - 干嘛
- Phoebe.         - Yeah?
快看窗边那个男的 哇
Look at that guy by the window. Wow!
他真的好矮 而且我想他在自言自语
He's awfully short. And I think he's talking to himself.
老实说 他的床上功夫不怎么样
And to be completely honest, he's not that good in bed.
我最近是怎么了 我对我看到的每个男人心动
Ugh, what is wrong with me lately? It's, like, every guy I see.
譬如说那个男的
Look at that guy, for example.
他不是我喜欢的那一型
Normally that's not someone that I would be attracted to.
但现在我觉得…
But right now, with the way I'm feeling...
我想撕开他的运动裤跟霹雳包
...all I wanna do is rip off his sweatpants and fanny pack.
等一下 你怀孕大概四个月了吧
Wait a second! This is about the fourth month of your pregnancy, right?
- 对   - 这真的很正常
- Yeah.     - This is completely normal.
怀孕四个月时 你的荷尔蒙会很混乱
Around the fourth month, your hormones go crazy.
- 真的吗 你也会这样    - 没错
- Really? So this happened to you?     - Absolutely, yeah.
记住我怀的是三胞胎
And keep in mind, I was carrying triplets.
在医学上来说 我的症状要强上三倍
So in medical terms, I was thrice as randy.
原来是这么一回事
Wow, this explains so much.
上周末我走遍每一家店 坐在圣诞老人的膝盖上
Last weekend, I went from store to store, sitting on Santas' laps.
对 我记得我想要从运动鞋店偷走 …
Yeah, I remember trying to steal...
艾凡德·霍利菲尔德的人形立牌
...a cardboard cutout of Evander Holyfield from a Footlocker.
对啊
Yeah, ugh.
明天我得去看医生 我会问问她的
I go see my doctor tomorrow. I'll ask her about this.
或许她可以开个药给我吃
Maybe she can give me a pill or something.
对 那正是你需要的东西 你需要吃药
Yeah, that's what you need. A good pill.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi.
我把我们到洛克菲勒中心的照片洗出来了
Look, I got our pictures developed.
太棒了 乔伊 你想看我跟蒙娜去溜冰的照片吗
Oh, great. Joey, wanna check out pictures of me and Mona ice-skating?
通常我会想看 但现在我真的好忙
Oh, uh, ordinarily I would love to, but I am just swamped right now.
那个怪咸酥饼小贩帮我们合拍的照片在哪里
Where are the pictures that creepy pretzel vendor took of us together?
对 或许在最后面
Oh, yeah. Probably at the end.
天啊 他只拍了我的胸部
Oh, my God. All he took were pictures of my breasts!
我想看看照片
I'm missing picture time?
她长得也不错耶 罗斯
You know, she has a face, Ross.
- 我们这张合照很不错   - 那张真的很棒
- Okay, here's a good one of us.     - Wow, that is a good one.
看起来很像节日贺卡
Wow, It looks like a holiday card...
中间有树还有溜冰客跟雪
...with the tree in the middle and the skaters and the snow. Heh.
每年我都说我会寄节日贺卡 但我从来没有那么做
Every year I say I'll send cards and I never do it.
你要跟我一起寄出这张卡片吗
Do you wanna send this one out together?
一起寄我们的合照给大家
Together? Like, to people?
对 "佳节愉快 蒙娜跟罗斯上" 那一定会很棒 好吗
Yeah, "Happy Holidays, from Mona and Ross." lt'll be cute. Okay?
好吧
Heh. Uh, okay.
- 我得去上班了 待会打电话给我    - 没问题
- Oh, I gotta get to work. Call me later?     - Sure.
- 大家再见   - 再见
- Bye, guys.     - Bye.
- 再见   - 再见
- Bye.     - Yeah.
恭喜 你刚刚结婚了
Congratulations! You just got married!
我知道 你相信吗
I know. Can you believe that?
抱歉 一张节日贺卡有什么大不了的
I'm sorry. What's the big deal about a holiday card?
已婚夫妻跟家人才会一起寄照片
Married couples send out cards. Families send out cards.
约会了几个月的情侣不会一起寄卡片 她疯了吗
People who've been dating a few months do not send out cards. Is she crazy?
你说的人是你的太太
Hey, hey, hey. That's your wife you're talking about.
宾 宾太太
Bing! Ho, and the Bingette!
- 老婆 你记得我老板道格   - 对 嗨
- Honey, you remember my boss, Doug.     - Yes. Hi.
好消息 我已经离婚了 我今天早上签了文件
So, good news, the divorce is final. I signed the papers this a.m.
我不知道你离婚了 我很遗憾
I didn't know you were getting a divorce. I'm sorry.
遗憾 我终于可以离开那个苦牢了
Heh, sorry? Finally chewed my leg out of that bear trap.
- 恭喜你们   - 我们没有离婚
- Hey! Congratulations to you guys.     - Heh. No leg-chewing for us.
等着瞧吧
Well, give it time.
我们要庆祝离婚跟结婚
So! The divorce, the marriage, we got a lot to celebrate.
我们明晚何不一起吃晚餐
How about we go out to dinner tomorrow night?
我想不出来我们要做什么事
I can't think of anything we're doing.
为什么我想不出来我们要做什么事
Why can't I think of anything we're doing?
那么就说定明晚了 我六点可以离开法庭
Tomorrow night it is. I should be out of court by 6.
他们一直把性骚扰案丢给我…
They keep throwing sexual harassment cases at me...
我一直把他们打得毫无退路
...and I keep knocking them out of the park! Ha-ha-ha.
好吧 明天见
Okay, see you tomorrow.
你知道的 我们明天不能跟他见面
Just so you know, we're not seeing him tomorrow.
我没办法再跟他共度一个夜晚
I cannot spend another evening with that man.
你记得他在我们的婚礼上做了什么吗
Remember how he behaved at our wedding?
- 不记得   - 那是因为我们没有邀请他
- No.     - Because he wasn't invited.
因为他在我们的订婚派对上为非作歹
Because of the way he behaved at our engagement party.
对 他小便时直接喷中了冰雕 对吧
Oh, yeah. Boy, urine cuts right through an ice sculpture, doesn't it?
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi!     - Hey.
我去过冲印店了 你看
Hey, I went by the photo shop. Take a look.
这是卡片的初稿 你觉得呢
Here is a mockup of our card. What do you think?
那真的很棒
Huh. Wow, this is great.
你觉得我们该写上"爱你们的罗斯跟蒙娜"吗
Now, do you think it should say, "Love, Ross and Mona"?
我们还没有对彼此那么说…
Well, we haven't said that to each other yet...
但我猜跟其他人那么说 应该没关系
...but I guess it's okay to say it to other people.
- 你要多少张 我要一百张   - 一百张
- How many did you want? I'm getting 100.     - A hundred? Ha-ha-ha.
我猜我要…
Well, I, uh, guess I'll take, uh...
蒙娜
Mona?
我不确定印卡片这件事对不对
Uh, I don't... I'm not sure about the whole, uh, card thing.
真的吗 为什么
Really? Why not?
我们一起寄节日贺卡
Sending out a holiday card together?
我不知道我们是不是到了那个地步
I just don't know if we're really quite there yet.
我没想到那一点 你说的对
I didn't think of it that way. You're right. You're right.
- 我能问你一个问题吗    - 好啊
- So can I ask you a question?     - Yeah.
我们到了哪个地步
Where are we?
我们到了哪个地步 这段关系会有什么结局
You know, where are we? Where is this relationship going?
我喜欢跟你在一起 我只是希望我们往前走
I mean, I love spending time with you. I hope we're moving forward.
我们该谈一谈 你不觉得吗
We should talk about that, don't you think?
我们一起印卡片吧
Let's do the card!
- 什么    - 卡片 我想我们到了那个地步
- What?     - The card! I think we're there.
好吧 但我还是觉得我们应该谈一谈
Okay, but I still think we should have this conversation.
真的吗 即使我们印了卡片
Really? I mean, even with the card?
- 你好   - 你好
- Hi.     - Hi.
朗医生今天没办法过来
Just so you know, Dr. Long can't be here today. She was called to the hospital.
辛夫医生会帮你检查
So Dr. Schiff will be seeing you.
好吧 我能问你一个问题吗
Okay. Can I ask you a question?
是我有问题 还是帮我抽血的那个家伙真的很帅
Was it me, or was the guy who took my blood sample really cute? Heh.
你知道我在说谁吗 那个马桶盖头 手指都是毛的家伙
You know who I'm talking about? Bowl haircut, hairy fingers?
- 你好 瑞秋 我是辛夫医生   - 你就是啊
- Hi, Rachel. I'm Dr. Schiff.     - Yes, you are.
情况如何
So how's it going?
真的很不错 但别谈我了
Oh, it's really good. But enough about me! Come on. Heh.
你是哪里人 你是做哪一行的
Where are you from? What do you do?
- 我是医生   - 对 我是指…
- I'm a doctor.     - Right. I meant...
你有空的时候 你会煮饭或滑雪吗
...you know, in your spare time. Do you cook? Do you ski?
或你会跟太太 还是女朋友一起出去玩
Or hang out with your wife or girlfriend?
我没有太太或女朋友 但我很喜欢滑雪
Uh, I don't have a wife or girlfriend, but I do like to ski.
我喜欢滑雪 那真的很神奇吧
I love to ski! How amazing is this?
- 你觉得不舒服吗    - 不 我非常舒服
- Are you experiencing any discomfort?     - No, I'm very comfortable.
- 放屁会不舒服吗    - 不会
- Any painful gas?     - No!
辛夫医生 那是哪门子的问题
Ew, Dr. Schiff! What kind of question is that?
好吧 麻烦你躺下来
Okay, then. Would you like to lie down on the table?
你要我躺下吗
Would you like me to lie down on the table?
- 这是怎么一回事    - 你也感觉到了吗
- Sorry, is there something going on here?     - Do you feel it too?
- 嗨   - 那个…
- Hi.     - Oh, hey. So...
- 门诊看得如何    - 让我想一想
...how did your doctor's appointment go?     - Well, let's see.
今天他们派了一个帅哥医生给我
Uh, they gave me "cute boy" doctor today.
检查到一半 我用手指指着他下巴的酒窝中
In the middle of the exam I put my pinkie in his chin dimple.
- 天啊   - 你为什么要那么做
- Oh, my God!     - Why did you do that?
还记得我怀孕四个月时出的那个小问题吗
Okay, remember that problem I was having during my fourth month of pregnancy?
对 艾凡德·霍利菲尔德的人形立牌
Oh, yeah, the Evander Holyfield phase.
天啊 你真的很难受 你甚至想泡我
Oh, man. You were so hard up, you practically came on to me.
少做梦了
You wish!
如果我真的要你 我可以把上你
Hey, I could've had you if I wanted you.
是吗 来试试看吧
Oh, yeah? Come and get it.
好了 连这段对话都能挑起我的欲望
Okay, even this is turning me on.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Oh, hey.
罗斯 你跟蒙娜还好吧
Hey, Ross. How's it going with you and Mona?
你们还在一起吗
You guys still together?
对 我们有所进展 你会接到我们的卡片
Oh, yeah, we're moving forward. You'll be getting our card.
你们要一起寄节日贺卡
You and Mona are doing a holiday card together?
我们不只要寄节日贺卡
We're not just doing a card.
她还要谈一谈我们的交往会有什么结局
She also wants to have the conversation about where the relationship is going.
女人
Ugh, women.
我知道 为什么你们需要谈一谈
I know! Why do you guys need to have this conversation, huh?
懂得自我尊重的男人不会问女人"我们会有什么结局 "
No self-respecting man would ask a woman, "So where is this going?"
罗斯 你问过我
Uh, Ross, you asked me that.
你像是本没打开的书 好吗 我不会读心术
Hey, you were a closed book, okay? I'm not a mind reader!
而且我讨厌谈那些事 我真的不太会应付那些事
Besides, I hate those conversations. I'm horrible at them, really.
或许我需要暗示她…
Maybe I need some kind of a gesture.
我们的确有进展 不必去谈这件事
Something that says we're moving forward without having to talk about it.
- 像是请她搬去跟你一起住    - 比那个小
- Like asking her to move in with you?     - Wha...? Ha. Smaller than that.
- 帮她录录音带    - 比那个大
- Making her a mix tape?     - Uh, bigger than that.
- 给她你家的钥匙   - 我们比较接近录音带
- Give her a key to your apartment.     - Whoa, hello. We were closer with the tape.
你说过"我爱你"吗 你可以说"我爱你"
Have you said "I love you"? Say, "I love you."
我想我还没有到那个地步
I don't... I don't think I'm quite there yet.
但我可以说 "我喜欢跟你在一起"
But, oh, I could say, "I love spending time with you."
- 我们讨厌那句话   - 那像是被人打了一巴掌
- No, we hate that.     - That is a slap in the face.
算了 你们知道吗 我会跟她谈
Oh, forget it. You know what? I'll just have the conversation.
我会说我喜欢我们现在的样子 并怀着最好的期待
I'll just say, "I like things the way they are," and hope for the best.
你觉得呢 瑞秋
What do you think, Rach?
我想 如果这里冷一点…
I think if it was a little colder in here...
我可以看到你的乳头硬起来
...I could see your nipples through that sweater.
宾 我们今晚八点出发
Bing, we're all set for tonight. 8:00.
我们没办法去 摩妮卡得上班
Oh, uh, as it turns out, we can't do it. Monica has to work.
我前妻不上班
Oh. My ex-wife didn't work.
除非你说回娘家是"上班"
Unless you call turning into her mother "work."
好吧 那么明天晚上
Now, fine. Tomorrow night, then.
她明晚也不能来
Oh, uh, well, tomorrow's no good for her, either.
为什么
Oh? Why not?
她的草地保龄球巡回赛
It's the semifinals...
要打…
...of her...
准决赛
...bocce ball tournament.
- 啊   - 发生了什么事 宾
- Ahem.     - What's going on, Bing?
你老婆不喜欢我吗
Does, uh, your wife have a problem with me, or something?
你说的太夸张了
Well now you're just talking crazy.
我们三个为什么不能一起出去
Then why can't the three of us go out together?
因为我们分居了
Because, uh, we split up.
摩妮卡跟我分居了
Monica and I split up.
抱着我
Hold me.
天啊 宾
Good God, Bing.
我不能说我很惊讶
Well, I can't say I'm altogether surprised.
我看到她看你的眼神 就知道她不爱你
I saw the way she looked at you, and there was no love there.
她看着我时充满了欲望
And the way she looked at me, pure lust.
在这种时候只有…
What would help me through this tough time...
掐人才能让我泄愤 我可以掐你吗
...is choking someone. Can I choke you?
宾 孩子 我们得让你忘了这件事
Bing, my boy, we're gonna get you over this.
我有个计划 拿着你的外套 我们去脱衣舞俱乐部
Here's the plan: Grab your coat, we're going to a strip club!
不 摩妮卡会生气的
Oh, no, Monica would freak.
但谁管那个臭女人呢
But to hell with that bitch!
咖啡来了
Here we go.
蒙娜
Ah, Mona, um...
我们该来谈谈我们之间了
...I think it's time we had a conversation about where things are with us.
我想那是我提出的建议
Yeah, I think I suggested that.
我们非常…
Heh. Uh, we are so...
那么…
So, um...
我真的很喜欢你
...well, I really like you.
我喜欢跟你在一起
And I love, um, you know, hanging out with you.
我非常开心
And I'm having a lot of fun.
好吧
Okay.
如果只是为了好玩 我们就不必交往了
I mean, there's no point in spending time with someone if it's just fun.
我们得有结果 对吧
It's gotta be going somewhere, right?
我们会有什么结果
So where is it going?
那真是个问题
That's the real question.
答案是…
And the answer is...
我们会…
...it's going somewhere...
很好玩
...fun.
我知道你在想什么 10年前你只想玩玩
I know what you're thinking. Fun was fine for you 10 years ago.
但现在你不年轻了
But you're not getting any younger.
我不是说你 不是你 你越来越年轻了
No, I mean, not you. Not you. You are getting younger!
你每一秒都在变年轻 你有什么秘诀
You look like you're getting younger by the second. What's your secret?
抱歉 我们是什么关系
I'm sorry, so, uh, where are we?
总而言之…
Well, to sum up:
我们很开心 你看起来很年轻
We're having fun. You look young.
- 好吧   - 但那是不够的
- Okay...     - But that's not enough.
所以…
So, heh, so...
这是我家的钥匙
...here's a key to my apartment.
- 真的吗    - 真的
- Really?     - Really.
你不觉得太快了吗
You don't think this is too fast?
你给她你家的钥匙
You gave her a key to your apartment?
不只是那样 我给了她我唯一的钥匙
Not just a key, I gave her the only key!
现在我是个很认真谈恋爱 无家可归的家伙
I am now a homeless person in a very serious relationship.
- 罗斯 你们谈的如何    - 很棒 现在我流落街头
- Oh, Ross, how'd the conversation go?     - Great. I live on the street.
哪里
Where?
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey!     - Hi.
好 摩妮卡 瑞秋 他是我朋友罗杰
Okay, Monica, Rachel, this is my friend Roger.
- 嗨 罗杰   - 嗨 罗杰
- Hi, Roger.     - Hi, Roger.
- 你好   - 我去拿饮料
- Hi.     - So, um, I'm gonna get us some drinks.
你能帮我吗
- Okay.     - Could you help me?
好吧
Yeah, okay.
他是来跟你做爱的
Um, he's here to have sex with you.
- 什么    - 别客气
- What?     - You're welcome.
菲比 不
Phoebe, no!
没关系 他是个处男
It's okay. He's a virgin.
瑞秋 我跟这个家伙提过
Rachel, um, I was talking to this guy...
- 我想他会跟你做爱   - 这个…
...and I think he'll have sex with you.     - Okay...
让他们两个独处一下吧
Yeah, okay. Let's leave these two alone.
不 我不在乎我的荷尔蒙在做什么
No. I don't care what my hormones are doing.
我不会随便跟男人上床
I'm not gonna just do it with some random guy.
好吧 那么你去告诉罗杰 因为他真的很期待
Fine. Then you tell Roger. He was really looking forward to this.
宾 看看那对双胞胎姊妹一起跳舞
Ooh, Bing, look at those twin sisters dancing together.
我出钱请她们 坐在你大腿上跳舞
Let me buy you a lap dance with those girls, huh?
没关系 只有一个女孩在跳舞
That's all right, sir. And that's just one girl.
宾 这是什么
Bing, what's this?
那是一只手 是你用来拿酒的东西
It's a hand. It's a thing you use as a Jack and Coke holder.
那是婚戒 把它丢了
No, it's a wedding ring. You gotta get rid of it.
我们把它丢到东河去
We're gonna go to the East River and throw it in!
- 不   - 要
- Oh, no, no, no!     - Yeah, yeah!
我那么做了 那让我觉得好多了
I did, and I felt a hell of a lot better!
你甚至可能会打中海鸥
If you whip it right, you might hit a seagull in the head.
好吧 我需要一堆备用钥匙
Okay. Oh, I'm gonna need a bunch of extra keys.
很明显地 我会毫无理由地将它们送人
Apparently, I give them away for no reason at all.
罗斯 发生了什么事  你在换锁
Hey, Ross, what's going on? You changing the lock?
不
No, heh.
是那个家伙在换锁
That guy is.
我不懂
I don't understand.
你把你家的钥匙给我 然后你换了锁
You give me a key to your apartment and then change the lock?
祝你好运
Good luck, buddy.
我以为我们往前迈进了一步
Um, I thought we were moving forward.
你给我完全混乱的讯息
And now you're sending me all these mixed signals.
你到底想告诉我什么
What are you trying to tell me?
我想告诉你…
I'm trying to tell you...
我帮你录了一卷录音带
...I made you a mix tape.
- 什么    - 我爱你
- What?     - I love you.
我喜欢跟你在一起
And I love spending time with you.
- 老婆 我回来了   - 你从龙舌兰酒工厂回来
- Hi, honey, I'm home.     - From the tequila factory?
那真的好可怕
It was awful.
为了逃避跟道格的晚餐约会 我告诉他你跟我分居了
To get out of dinner with Doug, I told him you and I split up.
他拖我去脱衣舞俱乐部 还有色情酒吧
So he took me to all these strip clubs and sleazy bars.
我不肯把婚戒交给他 他用汽水罐丢小鸟
And when I wouldn't give him my wedding ring, he threw a soda can at a bird.
过来 我可以用嘴巴呼吸
Come here. I can breathe through my mouth.
你知道最糟糕的是什么吗
Know what the worst part was?
我可以看到没有你的生活
I got to see what my life would be like without you.
那像是有贴身舞的 "风云人物"
It was like It's a Wonderful Life with lap dances.
请答应我 你永远不会离开我…
Please promise me that you'll never leave me...
我们会一起变老 相伴一生
...that we'll grow old together, and be with each other the rest of our lives.
我答应你
I promise.
说到相伴一生 我们今年一起寄节日贺卡吧
Hey, speaking of together, how about we send out a holiday card this year?
我不知道我们是不是到了那个地步
Ooh, I don't know if we're there yet.
我想订比萨 我能问你一个问题吗
Yes, I'd like to order a pizza. Can I ask you a question?
今晚是那个金发帅哥外送吗  长得又酷又时髦的那个
Is the cute blond guy delivering tonight? Very "Abercrombie & Fitch."
- 我再打给你   - 你在跟谁讲电话
- I'll call you back.     - Who was that?
- 我在订比萨   - 你挂掉比萨店的电话
- Just the pizza place.     - You hung up on the pizza place?
我不会挂掉你朋友打来的电话
I don't hang up on your friends.
- 抱歉 今天我很不好受   - 怎么了
- Sorry, I'm just having a rough day.     - Oh. What's wrong?
- 你不会想听的   - 不然我为什么要问
- Oh, you really don't wanna hear about it.     - Then why did I ask?
这真的很丢脸
Okay. It's just that this is really embarrassing.
但最近自从我怀孕后…
But lately with this pregnancy thing...
我发现自己…
...I'm just finding myself...
我该怎么说呢
How do I put this? Um...
春情大发
Erotically charged.
那是"好色"的学名吗
Is that college talk for "horny"?
对 我有那样的感觉
Yeah. So, you know, I have all of these feelings...
不知道该怎么办
...and I don't know what to do about them.
我没办法像正常人去约会
Because I can't date like a normal person.
没关系 因为我不需要男朋友
Which is fine, I don't need a relationship.
我只要一夜情 我只要性
All I really want is one great night. Just sex.
没有牵绊 没有责任
You know? No strings attached. No relationship.
跟我喜欢的人在一起 他得知道他在做什么
Just with someone I feel comfortable with and who knows what he's doing.
只要疯狂度过一夜 那真的那么难…
For just one great night. I mean, is that really so hard...
找到吗
...to find?
你今天过得如何
So how was your day?
很好 我看见一只大鸽子
Good. I, uh, saw a pretty big pigeon.
我还得早起 快七点了
I gotta get up early, and it's almost 7:00.
我得回房了
Yeah, I gotta go to my room too.
- 晚安   - 晚安
- Okay, good night.     - Good night!
- 我不能那么做   - 我没有要你那么做
- I can't do it!     - I didn't ask you to!
- 你是瑞秋   - 你是乔伊
- You're Rachel!     - You're Joey!
- 你是我的朋友   - 你也是我的朋友
- You're my friend! Yeah.     - Right back at you.
对 而且那是不对的 那既奇怪又糟糕
Plus, it would be wrong, and weird and bad!
糟糕 但我不知道你在说什么 我没有要求你做什么事
So bad! I don't know what you're talking about. I didn't ask you to do anything.
我知道
I know!
- 你想做吗    - 不
- You wanna do it?     - No!
- 我也不想 我只是在考验你   - 那么就这样了
- Me neither, I'm just testing you!     - That's the end of this conversation!
- 我们没谈过这件事   - 没错
- This conversation never happened.     - Never happened.
- 晚安   - 晚安
- Good night.     - Good night!
快回你房里
Get back in there!
听着 关于罗杰的事 我很抱歉
Hi. Listen, ahem, I'm sorry about that whole thing with Roger.
那真的是不对的 我想弥补你
It really wasn't right, and I wanna make it up to you.
我带了一样…
So, um, I brought you something...
我觉得你会喜欢的东西来
...that I think you'll really enjoy. Okay.
我只是借给你用 好吗 我会把它拿回去的
Now this is just a loan, okay? I'm gonna want him back. So...
我得走了
I'm gonna go now.
抱歉 我以为我办得到 但我不能
I'm sorry, I thought I could do it, and I can't.